My name is Walt Case I own Card Traders of Austin in Austin Texas.
We've been in business for about sixteen years and sell a variety of sports cards.
One of the questions that's frequently asked is how do I buy baseball cards.
You can buy baseball cards in any number of ways.
You can certainly buy them from a hobby shop like mine.
Where you have a chance to come in and look at the cards, see what the cards look like.
Determine if it's a card that you would like to collect based on the price of the card.
And based on the design of the card.
You can also buy cards through the internet.
There are a number of internet sites that allow you to do that.
There are also card shows that are held nationally all over the country where dealers set up and you can buy cards.
You can also buy cards from individuals.
So there are any number of ways to purchase your baseball cards.
The things I think you need to lookout for is always buy cards from someone you can trust.
Whether it be your local hobby store, or someone that you developed a relationship with online.
Or through a card show.
Also the trust factor becomes very critical if you are buying expensive cards to make sure you are not buying a counterfeit card.